<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>amyxliu</title>
    <link href="https://amyxliu.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://amyxliu.github.io" />
    <updated>2023-12-27T15:57:37-08:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Amy Liu</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://amyxliu.github.io</id>

    <entry>
        <title>hi, i&#x27;m amy</title>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Liu</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://amyxliu.github.io/hi-im-amy/"/>
        <id>https://amyxliu.github.io/hi-im-amy/</id>

        <updated>2023-12-27T15:57:37-08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    welcome to my personal website. I am a third year graduate student at UW in the Department of Atmospheric Sciences advised by Abby Swann in the Ecoclimate Lab. My research interests are plant-climate interactions and how plants impact atmospheric composition in an urban setting.&nbsp;My recent&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p>
    welcome to my personal website.
  </p>

  <p>
    I am a third year graduate student at UW in the <a href="https://atmos.uw.edu/" target="_blank">Department of Atmospheric Sciences</a> advised by <a href="https://atmos.uw.edu/faculty-and-research/core-faculty/abigail-swann/" target="_blank">Abby Swann</a> in the <a href="https://www.atmos.washington.edu/~aswann/LabWebsitePublic/" target="_blank">Ecoclimate Lab</a>. My research interests are plant-climate interactions and how plants impact atmospheric composition in an urban setting.&nbsp;My recent work is on understanding the global plant carbon-water tradeoffs using Earth System Model (ESM) simulations.
  </p>

  <p>
    Previously, I graduated with a BS in Chemistry from UC Berkeley's <a href="https://chemistry.berkeley.edu/home">College of Chemistry</a>, where I was fortunate to be mentored by Erin Delaria and advised by <a href="https://cohen.cchem.berkeley.edu/" target="_blank">Ron Cohen</a>. I have interned on the Small Molecule Analytical and Business Insights and Analytics teams at <a href="https://www.gene.com/" target="_blank">Genentech</a>/<a href="https://www.roche.com/" target="_blank">Roche</a>, where my work spanned from conducting early research and development of drugs to supporting the planning of clinical trials. I am grateful to be supported by a <a href="https://www.nsfgrfp.org/" class="" target="_blank">NSF Graduate Research Fellowship</a>.<br>
  </p>

  <p>
    
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
